Guide to the McKim Mead and White Architectural Records circa 1875-1950 PR 42
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Subseries II.C: 1968 Transfer
    - American Military Cemetery, Florence, Italy (Box 1 of 3) (Offsite-box II.451)
      General (923)
    - American Military Cemetery, Florence, Italy (Box 2 of 3) (Offsite-box II.452)
      General, cont'd (923)
    - American Military Cemetery, Florence, Italy (Box 3 of 3) (Offsite-box II.453)
    - Garden City Company (Box 1 of 3) (Offsite-box II.454)
      Gristede's Store (431); Lord and Taylor Store (432)
    - Garden City Company (Box 2 of 3) (Offsite-box II.455)
      Martin's Store (866)
    - Garden City Company (Box 3 of 3) (Offsite-box II.456)
      General (866)
    - Harlem Valley State Hospital, Wingdale, NY (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.457)
      General (1032)
    - Harlem Valley State Hospital, Wingdale, NY (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.458)
      Power House (1033); Medical and Surgical (1034); Disturbed Patients Building (1035)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, MA (Offsite-box II.459)
      Aldrich Hall; Baker Library; Kresge Hall; Morgan Hall Alterations; Robinson Hall (all 605)
    - Harvard School of Business, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.459)
      General (605)
    - Lebanon Steel Foundry, Lebanon, PA (Offsite-box II.460)
      General (505)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Offsite-box II.461)
      Mead Art Building (698)
    - Middlebury College, Middlebury, VT (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.462)
      Wright Memorial Theater (510)
    - Middlebury College, Middlebury, VT (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.463)
    - Middlesex Hospital, Middletown, CT (Offsite-box II.464)
      General (429)
    - Mutual Life Insurance Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.465)
      General (1107)
    - Webb & Knapp (Offsite-box II.465)
      United Nations Approach (1106)
    - National City Bank, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.466)
      General (375); 42 St and Madison Avenue Branch (375, 376)
    - New England Center Hospital, Boston, MA (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.467)
      Ziskind Research Labs (1102)
    - New England Center Hospital, Boston, MA (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.468)
      Ziskind Research Labs, cont'd; Farnsworth Building; Pratt Building; Ambulance Entrance; Gift Shop (all 1102)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.469)
      General (1100-4)
    - New York Institute for the Blind, New York, NY (Box 1 of 4) (Offsite-box II.470)
      Proposed Double House (774); Lower School (775)
    - New York Institute for the Blind, New York, NY (Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box II.471)
      Lower School (775); Garden House and Miscellaneous (776)
    - New York Institute for the Blind, New York, NY (Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box II.472)
      Apartment House #1 (777)
    - New York Institute for the Blind, New York, NY (Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box II.473)
      Apartment House #2 (778); Deaf Blind School (779)
    - United States Postal Service (Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box II.474)
      New York Post Office Remodeling (786)
    - United States Postal Service (Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box II.475)
      New York Post Office Remodeling, cont'd (786)
    - United States Postal Service (Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box II.476)
    - United States Postal Service (Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box II.477)
    - United States Postal Service (Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box II.478)
      New York Post Office Remodeling (787)
    - United States Postal Service (Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box II.479)
      New York Post Office General (14)
    - Morgan, Gerald (Offsite-box II.479)
      Residence (104)
    - National City Bank, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.479)
      55 Wall Street Branch; 640 Fifth Avenue Branch (all 916)
    - Lehigh University, Bethlehem, PA (Offsite-box II.479)
      General (1015)
    - Man O' War Monument (Offsite-box II.479)
      General (1017)
    - New York State Bar Association, Albany, NY (Offsite-box II.480)
      General (506)
    - Northwestern University (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.481)
      General (961)
    - Northwestern University (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.482)
      General, cont'd (961)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.483)
      Newark, NJ station; Pittsburgh, PA station (all 788)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.484)
      New York, NY station, Escalators (973); New York, NY station, Ticket Offices (974); New York, NY station, Long Island Section (975); New York, NY station, Restaurants, Lunch Rooms (976); World's Fair Property Development (977); Harrison, NJ station (980); General (981)
    - Savoy Plaza Hotel, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.485)
      General (597); Additions (598); Additional Stories (598 ½)
    - South Capitol Street Bridge, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.485)
    - Merrill, Charles E., Southampton, NY (Offsite-box II.485)
    - Trinity College, Hartford, CT (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.486)
      Miscellaneous Campus Walks, etc. (765); General (736); Dormitory (Jarvis) (737)
    - Trinity College, Hartford, CT (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.487)
      Field House (740, 741)
    - Tufts University, Somerville, MA (Box 1 of 3) (Offsite-box II.488)
      Posner Hall Dormitory (1105)
    - Tufts University, Somerville, MA (Box 2 of 3) (Offsite-box II.489)
      Posner Hall Dormitory, cont'd (1105)
    - Tufts University, Somerville, MA (Box 3 of 3) (Offsite-box II.490)
      Ballou Hall (no #?)
    - New England Medical Center, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.490)
      Bradford Hotel (1103)
    - Norwalk Hospital, Norwalk, CT (Offsite-box II.490)
      Student Nurses Dorm (1103)
    - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.491)
      Wharton School of Finance and Commerce (993)
    - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.492)
    - University of Vermont, Burlington, VT (Offsite-box II.493)
      Men's and Women's Dormitories (904); Gymnasium (proposed) (904) Science Building (904); College of Medicine (proposed) (904); Chapel (554); Library Extension (555); General (556); Slade Women's Dormitory (557); Fleming Museum (558); Engineering Building (559); Women's Dormitory at Redstone (560); Southwick Memorial (561)
    - Community House, Canaan, CT (Offsite-box II.494)
      General (533)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.494)
      General; Chapel Entrance Steps, Etc. (all 533)
    - Dill, Sir John, Monument, Arlington, VA (Offsite-box II.494)
    - Harriman Ripley & Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.494)
      63 Wall Street (533)
    - National Academy of Design, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.494)
    - National Hotel of Cuba, Havana, Cuba (Offsite-box II.494)
    - National Shawmut Bank of Boston, Boston, CT (Offsite-box II.494)
    - University of New Hampshire, Durham, NH (Offsite-box II.494)
    - New York Institute for Blind, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.494)
      Air Raid Protection; Animal Husbandry Building; Proposed Library; Manual Arts Building; General (all 533)
    - New York University, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.494)
      John Doe Institute of Oral Hygiene; ROTC Building; Engineering Building; Gould Auditorium; Gymnasium; Machine Shop and Forge; General (all 533)
    - Osborn, Mrs. William H (Offsite-box II.494)
      Residence (533)
    - Rochester Savings Bank, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.494)
    - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Offsite-box II.495)
      General (548)
    - Patterson, Carl V.S., Towanda, PA (Offsite-box II.495)
      Residence (548)
    - Racquet & Tennis Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.495)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Offsite-box II.495)
      Royal Trust Company Building (548)
    - St. Mark's School, Southborough, MA (Offsite-box II.495)
      Memorial Tablets (548)
    - Smithtown Library, Smithtown, NY (Offsite-box II.495)
    - Towanda Public Library, Towanda, PA (Offsite-box II.495)
    - Towanda Hospital, Towanda, PA (Offsite-box II.495)
    - Presbyterian Church, Towanda, PA (Offsite-box II.495)
    - Trinity University, San Antonio, TX (Offsite-box II.495)
      Competition (548)
    - Universal Atlas Cement Company (Offsite-box II.495)
    - State of Virginia (Offsite-box II.495)
    - National Cathedral, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.495)
      Statue (548)
    - West Indies Bank & Trust (Offsite-box II.495)
      William Thayer tablet (548)
    - United States Military Academy, West Point, NY (Offsite-box II.495)
    - Whitney, Payne, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.495)
    - Carnegie Corporation, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.496)
      General (534)
    - Johnson, Harold F., Prospect, KY (Offsite-box II.496)
      Residence (534)
    - Harvard Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.496)
      General (549)
    - State of North Carolina (Offsite-box II.496)
      State Capitol, Raleigh, NC (549)
    - Abbey Memorial (Offsite-box II.496)
      General (702)
    - Batsford Book Shop (Offsite-box II.496)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.496)
      Boiler House (702)
    - Brooklyn Battery Tunnel (Offsite-box II.496)
    - Boston Public Library, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.497)
    - University of Vermont, Burlington, VT (Offsite-box II.497)
      Fleming Museum Addition (900); Waterman Building (901); Memorial Gateway (902); General (903)
    - Horvath Mills Incorporated (Offsite-box II.498)
      Parking Garage; Television Studio and Offices; Buyers Center; Specifications; Estimates (all 911)
    - Jackson, Sidney R. (Offsite-box II.498)
      General (912)
    - City of New York, NY (Offsite-box II.498)
      Park Avenue Studies (913)
    - Henry Sears & Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.498)
      Office (914)
    - Webb & Knapp (Offsite-box II.498)
      Airline Building (915)
    - American Academy of Arts & Letters (Offsite-box II.499)
      National Institute of Arts and Letters (M1)
    - Bayonne School, Bayonne, NJ (Offsite-box II.499)
      General (M1)
    - Butler, Jospeh G., Youngstown, OH (Offsite-box II.499)
      Butler Institute of Art Gallery (M1)
    - 58th St. Hotel, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.499)
    - Franklin National Bank, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box II.499)
    - Harmonie Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.499)
    - McKinley Birthplace Memorial, Niles, OH (Offsite-box II.499)
    - Newbold, Thomas, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.499)
      Residence (M1)
    - Our Lady of Esperanza Church (Offsite-box II.499)
    - Willard, Joseph E., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.500)
    - Trinity Church, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.500)
      Brooks, Phillips, Monument (M2)
    - Burke Foundation, White Plains, NY (Offsite-box II.500)
      General (M2)
    - Hartford Theological Seminary, Hartford, CT (Offsite-box II.500)
    - Kings Mountain Monument, Kings Mountain, S.C. (Offsite-box II.500)
    - McCarren Park, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.500)
      Shelter (M2)
    - Minneapolis Museum of Fine Arts, Minneapolis, MN (Offsite-box II.500)
    - Panama Pacific International Exposition, San Francisco, CA (Offsite-box II.500)
      Court of Honor (M2)
    - 277 Park Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.500)
    - Post Graduate Hospital, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.500)
    - St. George's School, Newport, RI (Offsite-box II.500)
    - St. John's Church, Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box II.501)
    - Vanderbilt Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.501)
    - Kendall, William Mitchill (Offsite-box II.501)
      Tombstones (M3)
    - Fenner, B. L. (Offsite-box II.501)
      (M3)
    - McKim, C.F. (Offsite-box II.501)
      Miscellaneous (M3)
    - Richardson, William S. (Offsite-box II.501)
    - Mead, William R. (Offsite-box II.501)
    - Smith, J.K. (Offsite-box II.501)
    - Vanderbilt, Teunis J. (Offsite-box II.501)
    - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA (Offsite-box II.501)
      General (M3)
    - Wells, J.M. (Offsite-box II.501)
    - White, L.G. (Offsite-box II.502)
    - White, Stanford (Offsite-box II.502)
    - First Parish Church Unitarian, Cambridge, MA (Offsite-box II.502)
    - McKim, Mead & White (Offsite-box II.502)
      Miscellaneous Letters; Miscellaneous Prospects; Jobs; Miscellaneous (all M3)
    - Caldwell, E.F., Nashville, TN (Offsite-box II.502)
      General (M4)
    - State of Connecticut (Offsite-box II.502)
      Connecticut State Capitol (M4)
    - University of Rochester, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.502)
      Eastman School of Music (M4)
    - Fayette National Bank (Offsite-box II.503)
    - Gouverneur Dispensary, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
    - Lapsley Memorial, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
    - League for Political Education, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
      Town Hall (M4)
    - Marine Trust Company of Buffalo, Buffalo, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
      Bank of Buffalo Building (M4)
    - Matthews, Charles T., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
      Residence (M4)
    - Rollins, Phillip A., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
    - Satterlee, Herbert L., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
      Townhouse (M4)
    - Silk Center Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
    - Tiffany & Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.503)
    - University of Virginia (Offsite-box II.503)
      General; Archer Christian Memorial (all M4)
    - Whitney, Payne (Offsite-box II.503)
    - Worcester Art Museum, Worcester, MA (Offsite-box II.503)
    - City of New York, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      City Hall, Governor's Room (M5)
    - Sabine, Wallace C. (Offsite-box II.504)
      Acoustics; General (M5)
    - 383 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      General (M5)
    - Morton Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      681 Fifth Avenue (M5)
    - Century Holding Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      998 Fifth Avenue (M5)
    - McMillan, Mrs. G.N., Riverdale, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      Residence (M5)
    - Hamilton, Alexander (Offsite-box II.504)
    - Polifeme, A.C., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      Residence, 7 East 48th Street (M5)
    - Sampson & Proctor, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      Studio Building (M5)
    - Sherry, Louis, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      Restaurant and shop, 522 Fifth Avenue (M5)
    - Williams, Richard H., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.504)
      4 West 51st Street (M5)
    - Andover Free Christian Church, Andover, MA (Offsite-box II.505)
      General (M7)
    - Bennet Park (Offsite-box II.505)
    - Deutscher Verein, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.505)
      Clubhouse (M7)
    - Golf Courses (Offsite-box II.505)
      Layouts (M7)
    - Gotham Hotel, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.505)
    - University of Nevada, Reno, NV (Offsite-box II.505)
      Mackay Mining Building
    - National City Bank, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.505)
      55 Wall Street Branch (M7)
    - Reid, Whitelaw (Offsite-box II.505)
      Ophir Hall; Villard Houses; General (all M7)
    - Prospect Park, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.505)
      Shelter (M7); Entrance (no #)
    - Pyne, Percy Rivington, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.505)
      680 Park Avenue (M7)
    - Second National Bank, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.505)
    - White House, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.505)
    - Wuhu Hospital, Shanghai, China (Offsite-box II.505)
      Nauching Hospital; Shanghai Hotel; Shanghai Mission (all M7)
    - Bowditch, Ernest W. (Offsite-box II.506)
      General (M8)
    - North American Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.506)
      60 Broadway (M8)
    - Coolidge T.J. Jr., Manchester, MA (Offsite-box II.506)
      Alteration of Residence (M8)
    - Detwiler & Company Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.506)
      Brooklyn Tower, 11 Broadway (M8)
    - Lyons James, Monument (Offsite-box II.506)
    - New York Life Insurance Company (Offsite-box II.506)
    - Page, Thomas Nelson, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.506)
      Residence (M8)
    - St. Peter's Church, Morristown NJ (Offsite-box II.506)
    - Sherman Monument, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.506)
      Statue in Central Park (M8)
    - Slocum Monument, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.506)
    - Roger Williams Park, RI (Offsite-box II.506)
    - American Insurance Group Chemical Corporation (Offsite-box II.507)
      General (M9)
    - Asbury Park Auditorium, Asbury Park, NJ (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Offsite-box II.507)
      Decoration for visit of Prince of Wales (M9)
    - Benjamin (Offsite-box II.507)
      Residence (M9)
    - Boston Public Library, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Bradley, A.C. (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Breese, James L., Southampton, NY (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Bunker Memorial (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Fourth & First National Bank (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Gibson, C.D. (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Jones, D.R. (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Orange Free Library (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Shaw Monument, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Spier Falls Hydro Electric Plant (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Tacoma Hotel (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Walker (Offsite-box II.507)
    - Whitney William C., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.507)
      68 Fifth Avenue Residence; Roslyn, NY Residence (all M9)
    - Boston Symphony Hall, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.508)
      General (M10)
    - New York University, Bronx, NY (Offsite-box II.508)
      Library (M10)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Offsite-box II.508)
    - Denver Municipal Building, Denver, CO (Offsite-box II.508)
    - Detroit Centennial, Detroit, MI (Offsite-box II.508)
    - First Presbyterian Church, Chattanooga, TN (Offsite-box II.508)
    - Prince Henry Reception (Offsite-box II.508)
    - New England Trust Company, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.508)
    - Nickerson, George A. (Offsite-box II.508)
    - Radcliffe College, Cambridge, MA (Offsite-box II.508)
      Gymnasium (M10)
    - Rhode Island State House, Providence, RI (Offsite-box II.508)
    - United States Army War College, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.509)
      General (M11)
    - Athens Soldiers Monument (Offsite-box II.509)
    - Millet, Frank (Offsite-box II.509)
    - New York Public Library, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.509)
    - Norwalk Fountain, Norwalk, CT (Offsite-box II.509)
    - Redmond, Johnston L., Tivoli, NY (Offsite-box II.509)
      Residence Alterations, 1928-1929 (M11)
    - St. Gaudens, August (Offsite-box II.509)
      Residence (M11)
    - Stillman, James (Offsite-box II.509)
    - Washington Monument, Paris, France (Offsite-box II.509)
    - Woodward Statue, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.509)
    - Algonquin Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.510)
      General (M12)
    - Bowditch, Ernest W. (Offsite-box II.510)
    - Cheney, Anne W., South Manchester, CT (Offsite-box II.510)
      Residence (M12)
    - Langdon, Woodbury (Offsite-box II.510)
    - 8 East 56th Street (Offsite-box II.510)
    - Hill, Frederick E., architect (Offsite-box II.510)
      (M12)
    - Martyr's Monument (Offsite-box II.510)
    - Moore, Charles (Offsite-box II.510)
    - Morgan, J.P., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.510)
      Morgan Library (M12)
    - Palmer, Potter, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box II.510)
      Mausoleum, Graceland Cemetery (M12)
    - Pennsylvania Station, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box II.510)
    - Washington Park Commission, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.510)
      Mall (M12)
    - Benson, Arthur, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.511)
      Residence, 214 Columbia Heights (M13)
    - Jordan, John L. (Offsite-box II.511)
      General (M13)
    - Kimball, William W., Monument, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box II.511)
      Graceland Cemetery (M13)
    - King, George & Mary, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Kinney, Belle (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Lee Monument (Offsite-box II.511)
      Pedestal (M13)
    - Lenox School, Lenox, MA (Offsite-box II.511)
    - MacMonnies, F.W. (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Martiny, Philip (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Morgan, J.P., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.511)
      Morgan Library (M13)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, NC (Offsite-box II.511)
    - O'Connor (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Olmstead, A. H., Hartford, CT (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Parkman Memorial (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Patterson, Robert Wilson (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Payne, Colonel Oliver H. (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Pope, Alfred Artmore, Farmington, CT (Offsite-box II.511)
      Residence (M13)
    - Roanoke Rapids Power (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Scudder, Janet (Offsite-box II.511)
    - St. Paul's Church, Stockbridge, MA (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Tallant, Hugh (Offsite-box II.511)
    - University Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.511)
      Baths (M13)
    - Wetherill, Kate (Offsite-box II.511)
    - Church of the Ascension, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.511)
      General (M14)
    - United States Military Academy, West Point, NY (Offsite-box II.511)
      Improvements (M14)
    - Bronx Grit Chamber, Bronx, NY (Offsite-box II.512)
    - New York Public Library, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.512)
      Competitions (M14)
    - Miscellaneous Competitions (Offsite-box II.512)
      (M14)
    - Niagara Falls Power Company (Offsite-box II.512)
      Cottages (M15)
    - Finn, J. Wall (Offsite-box II.512)
      General (M15)
    - Elliman, Douglas L. (Offsite-box II.512)
      Residence (M15)
    - Bennett, T.G. (Offsite-box II.512)
    - Copley Plaza, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.512)
    - Players Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Pulitzer, Joseph (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Twombly, Hamilton McKay, Madison, NJ (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Architects Relations (Offsite-box II.513)
      (M15)
    - Architects Commission (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Architects Education (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Abbey, Edwin Austin (Offsite-box II.513)
      General (M16)
    - Adams, Henry, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.513)
      Memorial, Rock Creek Cemetery (M16)
    - Alden, R. Percy (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Arnold, B.W. (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Attributions (Offsite-box II.513)
      (M16)
    - Berkshire Marble Company (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Boston Gas Company, Boston, MA (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Brooks, Arthur (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Brown University, Providence, RI (Offsite-box II.513)
    - Canfield, A Cass (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Carroll, Royal Phelps (Offsite-box II.514)
      Yacht (M16)
    - Central Congregational Church (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Chubb, Percy, Brookville, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
      Ledgerstone (M16)
    - Coca-Cola (Offsite-box II.514)
    - College of Pharmacy, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Commonwealth Bond Corporation, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Emmet, C. Temple (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Fidelity Trust Company (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Garden City Hotel, Garden City, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Gibbs & Hill (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Ginn, Edwin (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Goodwin James J. (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Gorham Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Griffith Medallion (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Hopkins, Mark (Offsite-box II.514)
      Residence (M16)
    - Hotel Gabriel, Paris, France (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Hoyt, A.M. (Offsite-box II.514)
    - University of Illinois (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Hotel Imperial, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Knickerbocker Trust Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Lathrop, Francis (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Moore, E.C., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
      Residence, 8 East 44th Street (M16)
    - Moore, Mrs. William H., New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
      Residence, 4 East 54th Street (M16)
    - Munsey Building, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Nathan Hale Monument (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Osborn, Charles S., Mamaroneck, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Riverside Church, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Root, Robert K., Buffalo, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Sherry Hotel, London, England (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Symonds, Harvey D. (Offsite-box II.514)